Safa Eren Erdilli

Riga, Latvia ● +371 25642847 ● erenerdilli@gmail.com ● erenerdilli.com ● github.com/erenerdilli ● linkedin.com/in/erenerdilli

PROFILE

I am a Software Engineer with <u>5+</u> years of experience in IT, 3 years of which is backend development with <u>Java</u>. I have strong database knowledge and moderate <u>DevOps</u> skills. I am also developing enthusiasm for frontend development and trying to improve myself on React.

Main skills: Java, Spring Boot, REST, Hibernate, JUnit, Oracle, Postgres, Maven, Git, Jenkins, Redis, Docker, UNIX

Currently learning: AWS, React

WORK EXPERIENCE

03/2021 – present Software Engineer

Riga, Latvia **Accenture**

Application developer in a large fintech project running on agile methodology. Using Java and Spring. Having end-to-end responsibility, also takes part in deployment and

database operations.

Tech Stack: Java, Oracle, JSF, Maven, Git

05/2019 - 08/2020 **Software Engineer**

İstanbul, Turkey Borsa İstanbul

Responsible for development and maintenance of Market Data Dissemination module of

trading infrastructure in Istanbul Stock Exchange.

Tech Stack: Java 8, Maven, Oracle, Git

05/2018 - 03/2019 **Java Developer**

Istanbul, Turkey Gap Year/Personal Projects

Created and worked in various software projects. **Tech Stack:** Java, Spring Boot, Javascript, Postgres

01/2016 - 05/2018 Oracle Database Administrator Istanbul, Turkey Metod IT Academy

Worked as an Oracle Database consultant (remote and on-site) for more than 30 large

and medium scaled companies around Turkey.

Tech Stack: Oracle, SQL Server, UNIX

08/2015 - 09/2015 Intern Android Developer

Istanbul, Turkey Intertech Information Technology

Part of Mobile Banking Application Development team.

Tech Stack: Java, Android SDK, Android Studio

EDUCATION

09/2011 - 03/2016 Information Systems Engineering | Bachelor of Engineering

İstanbul, Turkey Dogus University

01/2014 - 06/2014 Computer Science | Bachelor of Science

Copenhagen, Denmark Copenhagen Business Academy

Erasmus Student Exchange Program